{
    "id": "2fee429ad95b4abca1b03961d79eb7f7",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have heard this …………………",
            "description": "Before can mean at any time before now/then.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "before",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c6f18c2969549a4a4e0e112fee9efde"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t heard anything from him ………………….",
            "description": "Lately means recently.",
            "answers": [
                "lately",
                "late"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "304ef461216b4d92a0d734aaae2080ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "He called me a few minutes ……………………..",
            "description": "Ago is used with a past tense and a time expression to count back from the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "470d457702264e208fb1274391e44f69"
        },
        {
            "question": "He once met me in Egypt. I have not seen him …………………..",
            "description": "We use since to reckon from a point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "then",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29cc9b52485b4e4da4e29990ac3b1823"
        },
        {
            "question": "That day he arrived ………………………",
            "description": "Late is the opposite of early.",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4beff9e5db848d6af9e06fb28680f90"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………. to do his best.",
            "description": "Adverbs of frequency usually go after the modal auxiliary verb and before other verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "tried always",
                "always tries"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f52d7ca2e78f4770803b9db82543004f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………….. mistakes.",
            "description": "Adverbs of frequency usually go after the modal auxiliary verb and before other verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "makes often",
                "often makes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e5ffed479b64721acac7d1d726b67c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………… for our purpose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough good",
                "good enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a18e74ca2aa456185c402d7082eeeba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient is …………………… worse today.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad. We use much to modify comparative adjectives. More is not possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "349e4f88e3c748a3940a5674c313cb82"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ambition urged me …………………..",
            "description": "Forward and forwards are both correct as adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "forward",
                "forwards",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "728b7fee311d43f1b36438ae6a099c17"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not walk so ……………………..",
            "description": "Fast is the adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5af7b9c9d4114483b101b37b2701bf15"
        },
        {
            "question": "The reason …………………….. I came here was to be with my family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "587252bf1da745a8abb68f4cb0c094f1"
        }
    ]
}